DAMILOLA JOSEPH DAVID

Address: Airport Road, Zone 7, Opposite Ikena Borehole, Lugbe, Abuja.

Tel: +2347030010299, +2348163356815

E-mail: damidj46@gmail.com, damidj47@gmail.com

Registered Nurse | ACLS | PALS | CPR | BLS Provider

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Registered Nurse with strong experience in delivering quality care to patients. Professional with more than 2 years of practice in emergency room care, medical care, pre and post-surgical recovery. Strong knowledge of pharmacology, and standards of care in the hospital or private practice setting. Caring and reliable person with a reputation for building a great rapport between medical providers and patients. Committed to making patients more informed and comfortable during their care.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Patient Assistant
- Stress Management
- Attention to Detail
- Compassion
- Safe Patient Transfer

- Wound Care
- Decision Making
- Recording Vital Signs
- Responding to Emergency
- Patient Focused Care

HARD SKILLS

- Microsoft Packages Such as Microsoft Office Suite
- Graphic Designing Using Photoshop, CorelDraw
- General Computer Application

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

HOME CARE MAR. 2021 - PRESENT

Designation: Home Care Nurse

Routinely record patient vitals during home visits. Administer medication and insulin, and completing blood pressure, glucose, urine, and stool tests. Inspect wounds, changing dressings, and handling personal grooming and hygiene. Test for muscle weakness, bedsores, and any signs of infection. Monitor patient recovery and compiling reports for the physician.

WUSE DISTRICT HOSPITAL

Designation: Registered Nurse

JAN. 2021 - PRESENT

Administer medication, intravenous therapy and other aspects of nursing care. Schedule patient admissions and discharges. Serve as a liaison between patient and doctor. Assess patient status and notify physicians of clinical changes. Maintain patient's charts and confidential files. Monitor and care for all pre and post operation patients. Assess, plan, implement and evaluate patient care using critical thinking and problem solving skills.

D&F HERITAGE HOSPITAL

Designation: Registered Nurse

MAR. 2020 - OCT. 2020

Handled care, safety, and long term health plans for 15+ patients. Commended 10+ time for efficiency and problem-solving skills by preceptor. Assisted patients with limited mobility in all necessary movement. Maintained 97% positive patient scores for compassion. Created assessments, diagnoses, and plan-of-care for high-volume of patients.

BLISS HOME CARE DEC. 2019 – MAR. 2020

Designation: Home Care Nurse

Implemented home health care procedures in accordance with employer guidelines. Assessed and charted observations of the patient's condition at each visit. Completed evaluation tasks, including reviewing medication and vital signs. Administered physician-prescribed medication. Dressed or redressed wounds and assessed the healing progress.

EDUCATION

ECWA COLLEGE OF NURSING AND MIDWIFERY, EGBE, KOGI STATE.

Registered Nurse 2020

PROFESIONAL MEMBERSHIP

• National Association of Nigeria Student Nurses and Midwives (NANSNM)

CERTIFICATIONS AND TRAINING OBTAINED WITH DATES

•	Basic Life Support Program	2021
•	Advanced Cardiac Life Support Program	2021
•	Pediatric Advanced Life Support Program	2021
•	Blood Borne Pathogen Program	2021
•	Cardiopulmonary Resuscitation	2021
•	Automated External Defibrillator and First Aid Program	2021
•	Integrated Management of maternal and Childhood Illness	2021

REFERENCES

Available on request.